<idea-plugin url="https://github.com/Eministar/faah-exception">
    <id>dev.eministar.fahsound</id>
    <name>FAH Failure Sound</name>
    <vendor url="https://github.com/Eministar">Eministar</vendor>
    <description><![CDATA[
Hear build and run results instantly across JetBrains IDEs.
<p><b>FAH Failure Sound</b> plays configurable audio cues for key IDE events, so you can stop watching output tabs and still notice failures, warnings, and successful runs.</p>
<ul>
    <li>Build events: failed, warning, succeeded</li>
    <li>Run/Debug events: failed, succeeded</li>
    <li>External build events: Gradle failed, Maven failed</li>
    <li>Per-event sound source: bundled, custom file, or no sound</li>
    <li>Per-event image/GIF source: bundled, custom file, or no overlay</li>
    <li>Per-event sound duration, per-event overlay duration, global volume, debounce, notifications, and optional image/GIF overlays</li>
    <li>Preset import/export and notification quick actions for Build, Run, and Problems tool windows</li>
    <li>Custom local <code>.mp3</code>, <code>.wav</code>, <code>.png</code>, <code>.jpg</code>, and <code>.gif</code> files from your IDE config folder</li>
    <li>Works as a platform plugin across JetBrains IDEs without requiring Gradle/Maven as mandatory dependencies</li>
    <li>No external services and no internal JetBrains APIs required</li>
</ul>
<p>Useful for quick feedback loops while coding, especially when builds run in the background.</p>
<p><a href="https://github.com/Eministar/faah-exception">Source code</a> | <a href="https://github.com/Eministar/faah-exception/issues">Issue tracker</a></p>
    ]]></description>
    <change-notes><![CDATA[
<p><b>1.1.2</b></p>
<ul>
    <li>Added per-event image/GIF settings, separate sound and overlay durations, preset import/export, and notification quick actions for Build, Run, and Problems</li>
    <li>Improved build-result routing so warnings no longer also trigger success sounds and higher-priority failures are not swallowed by global debounce timing</li>
    <li>Improved overlay media rendering and updated the plugin icon so the logo appears larger and less zoomed out in JetBrains IDEs and the Marketplace</li>
    <li>Kept the plugin compatible across JetBrains IDEs while continuing to bundle <code>error.mp3</code>, <code>succeed.mp3</code>, <code>cooked.jpg</code>, and <code>happy.gif</code></li>
</ul>
    ]]></change-notes>

    <depends>com.intellij.modules.platform</depends>

    <extensions defaultExtensionNs="com.intellij">
        <applicationService serviceImplementation="dev.eministar.fahsound.listeners.FaahLifecycleBootstrapService"/>
        <postStartupActivity implementation="dev.eministar.fahsound.listeners.FaahStartupActivity"/>
        <applicationConfigurable
                id="dev.eministar.fahsound.settings"
                displayName="FAH Failure Sound"
                instance="dev.eministar.fahsound.settings.FaahSettingsConfigurable"/>
        <notificationGroup id="faah.sound.notifications" displayType="BALLOON" isLogByDefault="true"/>
    </extensions>
</idea-plugin>
